Israeli billionaire Dan Guttler, who obtained Congolese cobalt mines through illegal and corrupt
means, then sold those cobalt mines to an Anglo-Swiss mining giant known as Glencore.
Glencore in turn has a deal with Tesla to provide Tesla the cobalt that it needs to produce its
electric vehicles. And so you see Tesla is paying Dan Guttler directly because Dan Guttler receives
$250,000 in royalties per day from the sale of this cobalt to companies like Tesla. And this
is in a country where more than 60% of the population lives in abject poverty. Dan Guttler
invests that money, those royalties, in two Canadian registered construction companies
that are involved in building illegal settlements in the West Bank. Dan Guttler is currently under
US sanctions, but the Biden administration wants to lift these sanctions because of its irrational push
towards the green and energy transition spearheaded by companies like Tesla. And so you see these
billionaire CEOs, these corporations are the policy makers. These corporations hold enormous power and
influence in our government. And that is something we have to realize before we start saying that boycotts
don't work. Free Congo.